Aufa Billah Putra Jazama

Depok, Jawa Barat • aufaroot18@gmail.com • 6285216392129 • linkedin.com/in/aufabillah

Summary

More than 1 year experience using Frontend Stack and 2 years experience as mentor (Assistant Lecturer). Currently working part time as Assistant Lecturer at STT Terpadu Nurul Fikri, teaching Frontend Programming Courses. Focus and strong knowledge on Frontend Stack using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React Technology.

Experience

STT TERPADU NURUL FIKRI

Depok, West Java Sep 2021 - Current

Assistant Lecturer

- Teaching frontend and backend programming courses
- Using React(Frontend) and Express (Backend) technology
- Responsible for teaching 145 students (Frontend) and 101 students (Backend)

YAYASAN ANAK BANGSA BISA - GOJEK

Jakarta

Frontend Engineer

May 2021 - Sep 2021

- Learning Frontend Stack from beginner to intermediate phase
- Frontend Stack: JavaScript, React, CSS Module, Redux, Testing
- Building Spotify Clone Website as final project

IQR FOUNDATION

South Tangerang, Banten

Jul 2020 - Oct 2020

Web Developer

- Design and Structure **IQR Foundation Website**.
- Using Figma to design websites and create design systems
- Using Wordpress and Elementor to build the IQR Foundation Website

Education

STT TERPADU NURUL FIKRI

Depok, Jawa Barat

Bachelor Degree, Informatics, GPA 3.86

2 September 2019

Thesis: Building Event Website using Laravel App

Certifications

BACKEND DEVELOPMENT AND APIS

Freecodecamp

Feb 2022 - No Exp

freecodecamp.org/certification/aufaroot18/back-end-development-and-apis

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER EXPERT

Dicoding

July 2021 - July 2024

dicoding.com/certificates/1RXYYYWDQXVM

Skills

• Frontend: HTML, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React

• Backend: PHP, Laravel, Node.js, Express

• Others: Linux, Figma